http://www.iawa.org/privacy/

Privacy Statement
The International Aviation Womens Association (IAWA) values your privacy and the following privacy statement covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by IAWA when you visit our website or when you purchase IAWA products and services online. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information.
Information Collection
IAWA collects personal information in order to deliver a superior level of customer service. In order to facilitate online transactions and allow user access to Members-Only features, IAWA collects certain information including names, addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, membership IDS, and credit card numbers. In addition, your personal information helps us to keep you posted on the latest meetings, products, and events that you might like to hear about.
The IAWA website requires you to provide personally identifiable information in order to use certain functions of the site. By providing such information, you consent to IAWA’s collection and use of it, as described in this Privacy Statement.
The information you provide may include information collected during the registration process, including contact information (name, address, phone number, e-mail address, dietary restrictions, certification status, website URLs and titles) and financial information (credit card number). This information will be used to process your order and, if necessary, to contact you regarding the status of your order.
We may provide limited personal information to the following trusted service providers to enhance our membership services and for the benefit of our members:
Survey Monkey, Crowd Compass, Doodle
Blue Host (hosting partner)
MemberLeap (AMS provider)
IAWA understands the importance of minimizing the amount of Personal Identifiable Information (PII) data it maintains and retains such data only as long as necessary. We maintain organizational record retention procedures, which dictate the length of data retention to meet business, legal and operational needs.
IAWA will not ask your permission to collect or use aggregate information about website visitors or users of our products and services since aggregate data does not identify you as a specific individual.
Request for data removal
Click here to request that IAWA remove your data or email info@iawa.org to be removed.
Information Disclosure
IAWA takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that IAWA does not sell or rent your e-mail address to other companies. To help us provide superior service, we may share personal information with credit card processing companies, merchants, and any other third party that may need the information for your request to be processed. These organizations have their own privacy and collection practices, and IAWA is not responsible for their independent policies. At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, the disclosure is necessary.
How to Opt-Out of IAWA Electronic Communications
We may from time to time send you information about our programs, products, and services via e-mail messages. If you no longer wish to receive our e-mail newsletter or promotional messages, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in the e-mail message or contact us at info@iawa.org.
Use of Cookies
Like many Websites, sportsbuilders.org uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of the Website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our Website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.
If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allow you to disable or enable the cookie feature. Please note that cookies may be necessary to enable you to use certain features on our Website.
Links
The IAWA Website contains links to other sites. IAWA is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected on our Website.
Information Security
IAWA will take every precaution to protect your personal information. All personal information collected on individuals will be kept confidential and in a secure environment. Access to personal information will be restricted to only those personnel with a legitimate business purpose.
Contact Us
By joining IAWA and consenting on this privacy policy you are giving us permission to process your personal data for membership services in IAWA and for purposes outlined above. You may withdraw consent at any time, or correct or update any of the information you provide to us at any time by sending an e-mail to info@iawa.org, or by calling 443-640-1056.
IAWA welcomes your comments and questions about the website, your experience with our site and services, and our Privacy Policy.
Connect, Inspire and Lead
19 Mantua Road • Mount Royal, NJ 08061856-599-8100• Fax 856-423-3420
© 2020 International Aviation Womens AssociationAll Rights Reserved. | Privacy | Terms of Use
